<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BookSwift</string>

    <string name="general_term_1">
        By accessing and placing an order with Go Travel,
        you confirm that you are in agreement with and bound by the terms of service contained in the Terms and Conditions outlined below.
        These terms apply to the entire app and any email or other type of communication between you and Go Travel.
    </string>

    <string name="general_term_2">
        Under no circumstances shall Go Travel team be liable for any direct, indirect, special, incidental or consequential damages,
        including, but not limited to, loss of data or profit, arising out of the use,
        or the inability to use, the materials on this site, even if Go Travel team
        or an authorized representative has been advised of the possibility of such damages.
        If your use of materials from  the site results in the need for servicing, repair or correction of equipment or data,
        you assume any costs thereof.
    </string>

    <string name="general_term_3">
        Go Travel will not be responsible for any outcome that may occur during th course of usage of our resources.
        We reserve the rights to change prices and revise the resources usage of policy in any moment.
    </string>

    <string name="license">
        Go Travel grants you a revocable, non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited license to download,
        install and use the app strictly in accordance with the terms of this Agreement.
        These Terms and Conditions are a contract between you and Go Travel.
    </string>

    <string name="terms_conditions">
        Cookie: A small amount of data generated by a website and saved by your web browser.
        It is used to identify your browser, provide analytics, and remember information about
        you, such as your language preference or login information.
\n\n
        Company: When this policy mentions "Company," "we," "us," or "our," it refers to the
        Booking App, the entity responsible for your information under this Privacy Policy.
\n\n
        Country: The location where the Booking App or its owners/founders are based; in this
        case, Malaysia.
\n\n
        Customer: Refers to the company, organization, or person that signs up to use the
        Booking App Service to manage relationships with consumers or service users.
\n\n
        Device: Any internet-connected device such as a phone, tablet, computer, or any other
        device that can be used to visit the Booking App and use its services.
\n\n
        IP address: Every device connected to the Internet is assigned a number known as an
        Internet Protocol (IP) address. These numbers are usually assigned in geographic
        blocks. An IP address can often be used to identify the location from which a device
        is connecting to the Internet.
\n\n
        Personnel: Refers to individuals employed by the Booking App or under contract to
        perform a service on behalf of one of the parties.
\n\n
        Personal Data: Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other
        information, including a personal identification number, allows for the identification
        or identifiability of a natural person.
\n\n
        Service: Refers to the service provided by the Booking App as described in the
        respective forms (if available) and on this platform.
\n\n
        Third-party service: Refers to advertisers, contest sponsors, promotional and
        marketing partners, and others who provide content or products/services that may
        interest you.
\n\n
        Website: The Booking App\'s site, which can be accessed via this URL.
        You: A person or entity that is registered with the Booking App to use the Services.

    </string>


    <string name="restriction">
        You agree not to, and you will not permit others to:
\n\n
        License, sell, rent, lease, assign, distribute, transmit, host, outsource, disclose,
        or otherwise commercially exploit the service or make the platform available to any
        third party.
\n\n
        Modify, create derivative works of, disassemble, decrypt, reverse compile, or reverse
        engineer any part of the service. Remove, alter, or obscure any proprietary notice
        (including any notice of copyright or trademark) of the Booking App, its affiliates,
        partners, suppliers, or licensors of the service.
    </string>

    <string name="payment">
By selecting any of our one-time payment plans, you agree to settle all fees or charges for the Service in accordance with the fees, charges, and billing terms effective when each fee or charge is due. Your Payment Provider agreement governs your use of the designated credit card account, and for your rights and liabilities concerning the Payment Provider, refer to that agreement rather than these Terms.
\n\n
Upon providing us with your credit card number and associated payment information, you authorize us to immediately verify this information and subsequently invoice your account for all fees and charges due under this agreement without requiring additional notice or consent. Any change in your billing address or the credit card used for payment should be promptly notified to us.
\n\n
We retain the right to adjust prices and billing methods, which will be effective immediately upon posting on our Site or communicated through email to your organization/\'s administrator(s). You are liable for any attorney fees, court costs, or collection expenses incurred in pursuing delinquent undisputed amounts.
\n\n
No contract for the Service is formed between you and us until we accept your order through a confirmatory email, SMS/MMS message, or another appropriate means of communication. You are responsible for any third-party fees incurred while using the Service.
    </string>

    <string name="return_refund_policy">
        Thank you for choosing to shop with us. We value your interest in our products and strive to ensure your experience is rewarding while exploring, evaluating, and purchasing them.
\n\n
        As with any shopping experience, certain terms and conditions govern transactions at our company. We will keep this concise within the boundaries permitted by our legal advisors. The key point is that by placing an order or making a purchase from us, you agree to these terms, in addition to our Privacy Policy.
\n\n
        If, for any reason, you find yourself unsatisfied with any product or service provided by us, please don/\'t hesitate to reach out. We/\'re here to address any issues or concerns you may have encountered with our product. Your satisfaction is our priority, and we/\'re committed to resolving any difficulties you may face.
    </string>

    <string name="suggestions">
        Any feedback, comments, ideas, improvements, or suggestions (collectively referred to
        as "Suggestions") that you provide to us regarding the service will be considered the
        exclusive property of ours. We reserve the right to utilize, adapt, modify, publish,
        or distribute the Suggestions for any purpose and in any manner without providing
        credit or compensation to you.
    </string>

    <string name="consent">
We have updated our Terms and Conditions to offer you full transparency regarding what is set when you visit our site and how it is utilized. By using our service, registering an account, or making a purchase, you hereby consent to our Terms and Conditions.
    </string>

    <string name="link_to_other_website">
Our service may contain links to other websites that are not operated by us. Clicking on a third-party link will direct you to that third party site. We highly recommend reviewing the Terms and Conditions of each site you visit. We do not have control over, nor do we assume responsibility for, the content, Terms and Conditions, or practices of any third-party sites or services.
    </string>

    <string name="cookies">
We utilize "Cookies" to track the areas of our website you have visited. A Cookie is a small data piece stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser. While not essential for using our service, Cookies enhance its performance and functionality. However, without these Cookies, certain features may become unavailable, or you might need to enter your login details each visit as we wont be able to recall your previous login. Most web browsers can disable Cookies, but doing so may limit or prevent access to some functionalities on our website. We never store Personally Identifiable Information in Cookies.
    </string>

    <string name="change">
You understand and agree that we retain the right to cease providing the Service (either permanently or temporarily) to you or to users in general, at our sole discretion, without prior notice. You have the liberty to discontinue using the Service at any time without the necessity of informing us explicitly. If access to your account is disabled, you may lose access to the Service, your account details, or any stored files or materials contained within it.
    </string>

    <string name="modification">
We retain the right, without liability to you, to alter, suspend, or terminate, temporarily or permanently, the service or any connected service, with or without notice.
    </string>

    <string name="update">
Periodically, we may introduce enhancements or improvements to the features and functionality of the service, such as patches, bug fixes, updates, upgrades, and other modifications collectively termed as "Updates." These Updates may alter or remove certain features or functionalities of the service. You agree that we are not obligated to (1) provide any Updates or (2) continue to provide or maintain specific features or functionalities of the service. Additionally, you agree that all Updates will (1) be considered an integral part of the service and (2) be subject to the terms and conditions outlined in this Agreement.
    </string>

    <string name="third_party_service">
We may present, incorporate, or make available third-party content (including data, information, applications, and other products/services) or provide links to third-party websites or services (referred to as "Third-Party Services"). By acknowledging and utilizing these Third-Party Services, you agree that we bear no responsibility for their accuracy, completeness, timeliness, legality, validity, copyright compliance, decency, quality, or any other aspect. We do not assume liability or responsibility to you or any other party for Third-Party Services. Third-Party Services and their associated links are provided solely for your convenience, and you access and use them at your own risk, subject to the terms and conditions specified by those third parties.
    </string>

    <string name="Term_and_Termination">
        This Agreement remains effective until terminated by you or us. We reserve the sole discretion to suspend or terminate this Agreement at any time, with or without prior notice, for any or no reason. Termination by us will be immediate upon notice if you fail to comply with any provision of this Agreement. You may terminate this Agreement by deleting the service and all related copies from your system. Upon termination, you must cease all service use and delete all copies from your system. Termination of this Agreement will not limit any of our rights or remedies in case of your breach of obligations under this Agreement during its term, whether in law or equity.
    </string>

    <string name="Copyright_Infringement_Notice">
If you are a copyright owner or an agent representing such owner and believe that any material provided by us constitutes an infringement on your copyright, please contact us and provide the following information:
        \n
a) A physical or electronic signature of the copyright owner or a person authorized to act on their behalf. \n
b) Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing. \n
c) Your contact information, including your address, telephone number, and email. \n
d) A statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the use of the material is not authorized by the copyright owner. \n
e) A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner. \n
        \n\n
Please send this information to [Contact Information] to report any copyright infringements. Upon receipt of a valid notice, we will promptly investigate and take appropriate actions.
    </string>

    <string name="Indemnification">
        You agree to indemnify and hold us, our parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, employees, agents, partners, and licensors harmless from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys fees, arising from or related to your: (a) use of the service, (b) violation of this Agreement or any law or regulation, or (c) violation of any third-party rights.
    </string>

    <string name="No_Warranties">
The service is provided "AS IS," "AS AVAILABLE," and with all faults and defects without warranty of any kind. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we, on behalf of ourselves, our affiliates, licensors, and service providers, expressly disclaim all warranties, whether express, implied, statutory, or otherwise. This includes all implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title, and non-infringement. We do not warrant that the service will meet your requirements, achieve any intended results, be compatible with other software, websites, systems, operate without interruption, meet performance or reliability standards, be error-free, or that any errors or defects will be corrected.
    </string>

    <string name="Limitation_of_Liability">
Our entire liability and your exclusive remedy for any claims shall be limited to the amount paid by you for the service. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we or our suppliers shall not be liable for any special, incidental, indirect, or consequential damages whatsoever. This includes damages for loss of profits, data, information, business interruption, or personal injury arising out of or related to the use or inability to use the service, third-party software/hardware used with the service, or any provision of this Agreement. Even if we or any supplier has been advised of the possibility of such damages. Some jurisdictions do not allow the limitation or exclusion of incidental or consequential damages, so the above limitations may not apply to you.
    </string>

    <string name="Severability">
If any provision of this Agreement is deemed invalid by a court of competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any term of this Agreement shall be deemed further or continuing, nor shall the failure to assert any right or provision constitute a waiver.
    </string>

    <string name="Time_Limitation">
Both parties agree that any cause of action arising from or related to the Services must commence within one (1) year after the cause of action accrues. Otherwise, the cause of action is permanently barred.
    </string>

    <string name="Waiver">
Failure to exercise a right or to require performance under this Agreement shall not affect a party ability to exercise such right or require such performance at any time thereafter. No single or partial exercise of any right shall preclude further exercise of that or any other right granted herein. In case of a conflict, this Agreement shall govern.
    </string>

    <string name="Amendments_to_this_Agreement">
We reserve the right to modify or replace this Agreement at our sole discretion. Material revisions will be notified at least 30 days prior to the new terms taking effect. Your continued use of our service after revisions implies agreement to be bound by the updated terms. If you disagree with the new terms, you are no longer authorized to use our service.
    </string>

    <string name="Entire_Agreement">
This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between you and us regarding the service, superseding all prior written or oral agreements. Additional terms and conditions may apply when using or purchasing other services, provided to you at the time of such use or purchase.
    </string>

    <string name="Updates_to_Our_Terms">
We may modify our Service and policies, necessitating changes to these Terms to accurately reflect our Service and policies. We will notify you before making changes to these Terms (unless otherwise required by law) and provide an opportunity to review them. By continuing to use the Service after the changes, you agree to be bound by the updated Terms. If you disagree with these or any updated Terms, you can delete your account.
    </string>

    <string name="Intellectual_Property">
Our platforms and their entire contents, features, and functionality (including but not limited to all information, software, text, displays, images, videos, audio, and design) are owned by us, our licensors, or other providers of such material, and are protected by Malaysia and international copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret, and other intellectual property or proprietary rights laws. Any unauthorized use of the material is prohibited without express prior written permission from us, unless otherwise provided in these Terms and Conditions.
    </string>

    <string name="Agreement_to_Arbitrate">
This section applies to any dispute except those relating to claims for injunctive or equitable relief regarding the enforcement or validity of your or Go Travel intellectual property rights. The term "dispute" means any disagreement between you and us concerning the Services or this agreement, in any legal or equitable manner. Notice of Dispute:
        \n\n
In the event of a dispute, you or us must give the other a Notice of Dispute. This written statement must include the name, address, contact information of the party giving it, the facts giving rise to the dispute, and the relief requested. Any Notice of Dispute should be sent via email to hongyanglim00@gmail.com. We will send any Notice of Dispute to your address if available, or to your email address. Both parties will attempt to resolve the dispute through informal negotiation within sixty (60) days from the date the Notice of Dispute is sent. After this period, arbitration may commence.
    </string>

    <string name="Binding_Arbitration">
If informal negotiation does not resolve the dispute, arbitration will be conducted exclusively as described in this section. You waive the right to litigate disputes in court before a judge or jury. The dispute shall be settled by binding arbitration following the commercial arbitration rules of the American Arbitration Association. Either party may seek preliminary injunctive relief from a court to protect its rights or property pending arbitration. The non-prevailing party will bear any costs incurred by the prevailing party.
    </string>

    <string name="Submissions_and_Privacy">
Any submissions or posts you make, including ideas, suggestions, designs, or information, will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary. Such submissions will become the sole property of us without compensation or credit to you. We may use these submissions for any purpose without obligation to you.
    </string>

    <string name="Promotions">
From time to time, we may include contests, promotions, sweepstakes, or other activities ("Promotions") governed by separate rules that may contain eligibility requirements. You agree to abide by these rules if you participate.
    </string>

    <string name="Typographical_Errors">
In case of typographical errors, we reserve the right to refuse or cancel any orders placed for products or services listed at the incorrect price. If your credit card has been charged for such a canceled order, we will issue a credit to your account in the amount of the charge.
    </string>

    <string name="Submissions_and_Privacy2">
When you submit or post any ideas, creative suggestions, designs, photographs, information, advertisements, data, or proposals, including concepts for new or improved products, services, features, technologies, or promotions, you agree that these submissions are non-confidential and non-proprietary. They become the sole property of ours without any compensation or credit to you. We, along with our affiliates, have no obligation concerning these submissions and can use them perpetually for any purposes, including developing, manufacturing, and marketing products and services.
    </string>

    <string name="promotions">
Occasionally, we may conduct contests, promotions, sweepstakes, or other activities ("Promotions") that might require you to provide personal information. Note that Promotions might have specific eligibility criteria, such as age or geographic restrictions. By participating, you agree to adhere to all Promotion Rules. Additional terms and conditions may apply to purchases made through the Services, which are part of this Agreement.
    </string>

    <string name="Typographical_Errors2">
In the event of an incorrect product or service listing due to typographical errors, we reserve the right to refuse or cancel orders placed for items listed at an incorrect price. If your credit card has been charged for a canceled purchase, we will immediately issue a credit to your payment account for the charged amount.
    </string>

    <string name="Miscellaneous">
Should any provision or portion of these Terms and Conditions be deemed unenforceable by a court of competent jurisdiction, the remaining parts will continue in full force. Any waiver of any provision here must be in writing and signed by an authorized representative of ours. We reserve the right to injunctive or other equitable relief without posting any bond or surety in case of breach by you. Our Service is operated from Malaysia and is not intended for distribution or use where it contravenes local laws or regulations.
    </string>

    <string name="Disclaimer">
We are not responsible for any content or code inaccuracies. We do not provide warranties or guarantees. In no event will we be liable for any special, direct, indirect, or incidental damages due to the use of the Service or its contents. Our Service and its contents are provided "as is" and "as available" without any warranties or representations, express or implied. We have no control over third-party content and make no warranties regarding its accuracy or reliability.
    </string>

    <string name="Contact_Us">
        If you have any questions, feel free to contact us:
        \n\n
        Phone Number: 0123456789
        \n\n
        Address: New Era University College
    </string>

</resources>
